Guide to the Christian Conference of Asia Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Publications, Series V
  - Periodical publications
    - East Asia Christian Conference
      - Signs of Christian Presence (Asian Christian Service), No date (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Christian Conference of Asia
      - Asian Christian Service Newsletter, 1971-1973 (Box 105, Folder 18)
      - Asian Ecumenical Communications Network, 1995-1996 (Box 105, Folder 19)
      - Asian Ecumenical News Service (from Communications Desk), 1975-1976 (Box 105, Folder 20)
        See additional issues in Series IV
      - Asian Issues (International Affairs), 1980 (Box 105, Folder 21)
      - Christian Education Newsletter, 1977-1981 (Box 105, Folder 22)
      - Education Bulletin, 1990-1991 (Box 105, Folder 23)
      - Education Newsletter, 1977-1985 (Box 105, Folder 24)
      - Mission and Evangelism Newsletter, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 25)
      - CCA News, 1973-1980 (Box 105, Folder 26-36)
      - CCA News, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - CCA News, 1986 July - December (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - Rural Youth - Occasional Newsletter of the Rural Youth Programme, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Theological Concerns Commission Occasional Bulletin - "Hayyim", 1979 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - Urban Rural Action, 1981-1987 (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - Voices (Urban Rural Mission), 1977-1985 (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - CCA Youth Occasional Newsletter - "Keadilan", 1983-1986 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Jointly-sponsored
      - Asian Movement for Christian Unity News (Federation of Asian Bishops' Conferences and CCA), 1996 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Pamphlets and brochures
    - East Asia Christian Conference
      - Miscellaneous, 1957-1973 (Box 106, Folder 16)
        Including "Joint Labourers in Hope - A Report of the EACC 1968-1973" by Kyaw Than and "Christ's Ministry and Ours" - The John R. Mott Memorial Lectures Series II
    - Christian Conference of Asia
      - Informational brochures, No date (Box 106, Folder 17)
      - Narrative Reports, 2001, 2002 (Box 106, Folder 18)
      - Asia Sunday pamphlets and posters, 1975-1982 (Box 106, Folder 19)
      - Liturgy for Human Rights Sunday, 1996 (Box 106, Folder 20)
      - Hymnal project - correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 106, Folder 21)
      - Niles Memorial Lecture by Rienzie Perera, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous - including "We and the Hungry Ones" and papers on theology, 1977-1978, no date (Box 106, Folder 23)
  - Lists of publications
    - "There is no end..." Checklist of EACC-CCA publications 1948-1981 by Dorothy M. Harvey, 1982 (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - EACC publications catalogs, No date (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - CCA publication catalogs and lists, 1975-1998 (Box 106, Folder 26)
- CCA Assemblies / Conferences, Series VI
  - General Assemblies
    - 1st General Assembly, Paraprat, North Sumatra, 1957
      - Congregational Quarterly article "The Prapat Conference, March 1957" by Leslie E. Cooke, D.D., LL.D. (photocopy) (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - Country papers, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 21)
      - Meaning of Prapat, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous papers post assembly, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 23)
      - Newscasts, 1957 (Box 24)
      - Papers at inauguration, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 25)
      - Participants, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 26)
      - "Pilgrims' Progress at Prapat" by Harvey L. Perkins and Winburn T. Thomas, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 27)
      - Pre-conference papers, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 28)
      - Significance of Prapat by F.S. De Silva, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 29)
      - Speeches, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - 2nd Assembly, Kuala Lumpur, Malaya, 14-24 May 1959
      - Actions and Findings of the East Asia Christian Conference, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 31)
      - Assembly workbooks, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 32)
      - Discerning Christ's work, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 33)
      - Miscellaneous papers, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 34)
      - Participants, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 35)
      - Program and daily schedule, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 36)
      - Speeches, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - 3rd General Assembly, Bangkok, Thailand, 1964
      - International Review of Missions article "Report from Bangkok" by G.C. Jackson, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 38)
      - Miscellaneous articles and reports, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - 4th General Assembly, Bangkok, Thailand, January 30-February 8, 1968
      - Constitutional matters, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - Interchurch Aid, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - Participants, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - Post assembly documents, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 17)
      - Program and assembly work books, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 18)
      - Resolutions - Vietnam, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - Sections, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 20)
      - Worship, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - 5th General Assembly, Singapore, June 6-12, 1973
      - Addresses and sermons, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Administration, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - General information, reports, finance, press releases, and worship, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Handbooks and workbooks, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Justice and service, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Justice and service, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Life and action, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Membership, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Membership of committees, message and communication papers, and life in action papers, 9 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - Minutes, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - Niles Memorial Lectures, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - Papers: J oint Labourers in Hope, Christian Action in the Asian Struggle by M.M. Thomas, and Asian Struggle for Justice, Liberation, and Development by Wen Yong Kang, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Pre assembly documents, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 16)
      - Sections, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      - Worship, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - 6th General Assembly, Penang, Malaysia, May 31-June 8, 1977
      - Addresses, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 19)
      - Bible studies, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 20)
      - Business Committee documents, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 21)
      - Communications, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 22)
      - Delegates, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 23)
      - Finance, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 24)
      - Justice and Service, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 25)
      - Life and Action, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 26)
      - Magazine and newspaper clippings, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 27)
      - Minutes, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 28)
      - Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 29)
      - Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 30)
      - News, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 31)
      - Niles Memorial Lectures, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 32)
      - Pre assembly documents, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 33)
      - Press, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 34)
      - Registration, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 35)
      - Reports, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 36)
      - Sections, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 37)
      - Speakers, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 38)
      - Worship, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 39)
      - Worship, 40 (Box 58, Folder 40)
      - Worship, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 41)
    - 7th General Assembly, Bangalore, India, May 18-28, 1981
      - Assembly News, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Bible studies, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Circulars, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Constitutional matters, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Delegates, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - General, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Minutes, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - News, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Niles Memorial lecture, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Papers, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Registration, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - Registration by country: Australia-Burma, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 14)
      - Registration by country: Hong Kong, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - Registration by country: India-Indonesia, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 16)
      - Secretariat, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 17)
      - Testimonies, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 18)
      - Women's Forum, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 19)
      - Worship, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 20)
      - Youth Forum, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - 8th General Assembly, Seoul, Korea, June 26-July 2, 1985
      - Assembly Planning Committee, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 22)
      - CCA constitution and proposed revisions, financial report, lists of speakers, and general information, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 23)
      - Circulars, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 24)
      - Contributors, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 25)
      - Delegate information: consultants, fraternal delegates, press, and visitors, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 26)
      - Delegate information and correspondence by country: general, Bangladesh, Burma, and Hong Kong, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 27)
      - Delegate information, registration, and correspondence: India, Indonesia, Korea, and Malaysia, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 28)
      - Delegate information, registration, and correspondence: New Zealand, Pakistan, Singapore, Sri Lanka, and Taiwan, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 29)
      - Documents, minutes, and notes of Clement John (CCA International Affairs desk secretary), 1985 (Box 59, Folder 30)
      - Documents, minutes, and notes of Clement John (CCA International Affairs desk secretary) (Box 59, Folder 31)
      - Documents, minutes, and notes of Clement John (CCA International Affairs desk secretary), 1985 (Box 59, Folder 32)
      - Evaluations, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 33)
      - Festival of Faith, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 34)
      - General, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 35)
      - General, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Niles Memorial lecture, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Registration, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Registration: Australia-Pakistan, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Registration: Philippines-Press, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Registration: Visitors-Staff, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Reports, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Reports, 1985 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Women's Forum, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Worship, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Worship, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - Youth Forum, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - 9th General Assembly, Manilla, Philippines, June 4-12, 1990
      - Bible studies, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - Development and Service assembly planning, 1989-1990 (Box 60, Folder 14)
      - Finance, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - Finance, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 16)
      - General, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 17)
      - Minutes, worship material, and bible study, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 18)
      - Papers, reports, nominations, assembly work book, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 19)
      - Registration, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 20)
      - Voting patterns, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Extra-ordinary General Assembly, Colombo, Sri Lanka, June 8-9, 1994
      - Daily schedule, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - 10th General Assembly, Colombo, Sri Lanka, June 8-14, 1995
      - Assembly preparatory meeting, budget, and documentation, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Bible studies, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Budget, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Communications, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - The Common Task and Our Common Obedience: Asian Churches in Christian Mission, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Constitution amendments, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, general, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence re. security in Sri Lanka and greetings, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Credentials Committee, worship theme, bible study, resource people, and Local Committee, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Documents distributed, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Documents distributed, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - General, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - General, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - General, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - Henriette Hutabarat's conference planning files, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - Nominations, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 19)
      - Participants and program materials, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 20)
      - Planning Committee, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 21)
      - Reports, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 22)
      - Schedules, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 23)
      - Terms of reference, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 24)
      - Worship, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 25)
      - Youth representation, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 26)
      - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - 11th General Assembly, Tomohon, Indonesia, June 2-6, 2000
      - General, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Preparation, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Program planning, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Proposed constitution amendments, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Towards New Thrusts and a New Structure for the CCA and proposed constitution amendments, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - 12th General Assembly, Chiang Mai, Thailand, March 31-April 6, 2005
      - Delegates nominated, 2004-2005 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Delegates nominated, 2004-2005 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Delegate registration: A-H, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Delegate registration: H-I, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Delegate registration: I continued, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Documents and reports, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - Registration forms, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - Registration forms, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - Overview, 2005 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - CCA-sponsored conferences
    Documentation of other conferences sponsored by CCA can be found under in Series IV under the various Program Areas.
    - 45th Anniversary Celebration, 2002 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - 45th Anniversary of the CCA & International Symposium on New Ecumenism, Hong Kong, August 5-9, 2002 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - AG-KED (Evangelical Church in Germany) and CCA Consultation on Hunger - Human Rights - Living Theology, Gomadingen, May 3-6, 1976 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Asia Mission Conference, Chiangmai, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Asia Mission Conference, Indonesia, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 9-10)
    - Asia Mission Conference, Indonesia, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Asia Mission Conference, Seoul, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 11-14)
    - Asia National Council of Churches General Secretariat Meeting, Delhi, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Asian Christian Spirituality discussion, Hong Kong, 1993 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Asian Church Leaders' Consultation on "Refugee Situation in Asia & Churches' Response," Madras, India, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Asian Conference on Church and Society, Seoul, 1967 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Asian Conference on Church and Society, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Asian Inter-church Aid Consultation, Hong Kong, 1963 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Asian Inter-religious Leaders Conference, Chiang Mai, Thailand, 2007 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Christian Art in Asia Consultation, Bali, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Christian Art in Asia Consultation, Bali: Committee Meetings, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Christian Art in Asia Consultation, Bali: Correspondence to Countries, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Christian Art in Asia Consultation, Bali: Correspondence to Countries, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - Christian Art in Asia Consultation, Bali: Pre-Conference Papers, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - Christian Art in Asia Consultation, Bali: Report, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Christians in Industry and Lay Training, Kyoto, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Church Leaders Conference, Kyoto, Japan, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Church Leaders Meeting, Bangkok, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Conference of the Churches of South East Asia -"Joint Action for Mission in Australia", 1963 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Congress of Asian Theologians: Convener's Groups, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Congress of Asian Theologians: Various, 1996-2000 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Congress of Asian Theologians: Various, 1997 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Congress of Asian Theologians: Various, 1999-2001 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Consultation Among Conservative Evangelicals and other Christians, 1970 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Consultation, "Equipping Local Churches for Mission", 1981 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Consultation on Asian Mission Support Program, 1994-1998 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Consultation on Buddhist-Christian Encounter, Rangoon, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Consultation on China, 1976 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Consultation on Confessional Families, Kandy, 1966 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Consultation on Ecumenical Sharing, Hong Kong, 1990 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Consultation on Education for Justice and Peace, 1992 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Consultation on Health, Healing and Wholeness, 1992 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Consultation on Mission and Evangelism, Hong Kong, 1975 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Consultation on the Mission of the Church, Christchurch, New Zealand, 1962 November (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Consultation on Tourism, Penang, 1975 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Ecumenical Partners meeting, Hong Kong, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Federation of Asian Bishop's Conference/CCA: Joint Task Force, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Federation of Asian Bishop's Conference/CCA: Various, 1993-1997 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Federation of Asian Bishop's Conference/CCA: Various, 1993-2001 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Global Roundtable Meeting, Hong Kong, 2001 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - ICCO (Interkerkelijke coördinatie commissie ontwikkelingsprjecten – Interchurch Co-ordination Committee for Development Projects)/CCA: An Ecumenical Forum, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Korean-German Consultation, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Media and Non-Formal Education, Manila, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Middle East Council of Churches (MECC)/CCA Consultation, Cyprus (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - Middle East Council of Churches (MECC)/CCA Consultation, Cyprus (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous meetings: Worship services, 1993-1994 (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous meetings: Worship services, 1995-1996 (Box 92, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous meetings: Worship services, 1997 (Box 92, Folder 25)
    - National Council of Churches: Women and Education Secretaries Meeting, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 26)
    - National Theological Conference on Worship, Manila, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Planning, Monitoring & Evaluation Worship, Hong Kong, 2004 (Box 92, Folder 27)
    - Roundtable meeting, Hong Kong, 1996 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Roundtable on Mission and Missiology, Hong Kong, 1999 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Roundtable meeting, Hong Kong, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Seminar on Christian Communication and Theological Education, Nagpur, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 28)
    - Situation Conferences (convened by East Asia Christian Conference), 1963 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Sub-Regional Ecumenical Leadership Workshop (1st), Bogoz, Indonesia, August 24-September 3, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Sub-Regional Ecumenical Leadership Workshop on Women (2nd), November 26-December 5, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Sub-Regional Workshop for Developing Ecumenical Leadership (3rd), Bangkok, Thailand, February 24-March 4, 1992 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Sub-Regional Workshop on Developing Ecumenical Leadership Among Women in Asia (4th), Seoul, Korea, October 19-26, 1992 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Related Organizations / Conferences, Series VII
  - Agency for Christian Literature Development, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Agency for Christian Literature Development: Joint Working Committee, Geneva, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - All Africa Conference of Churches, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 2-6)
  - Anglican Consultative Council / Council of the Church in East Asia, 1974-1987 (Box 79, Folder 7-10)
  - Asia Conference on Church and Society: Address list, papers, and correspondence, Darwin, Australia, 1999 (Box 93, Folder 2-3)
  - Asia Conference of Theological Students, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 4-6)
  - Asia Methodist Advisory Committee, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Asia-Pacific Baptist Fellowship, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Asian Alliance of YMCAs (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Asian Christian Art Association, 1980-1990 (Box 79, Folder 17-18)
  - Asian Christian Peace Conference, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Asian Christian Peace Conference, 1976 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Asian Church Women's Conference: administration including Constitution, 1979, no date (Box 93, Folder 7, 11, 12)
  - Asian Church Women's Conference: workshops and assemblies, 1974-1978 (Box 93, Folder 8-10)
  - Asian Church Women's Conference: Fellowship of the Least Coin, 1962-1978 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Asian Church Women's Conference: Fellowship of the Least Coin, 1979-1980 (Box 93, Folder 13-16)
  - Asian Church Women's Conference: correspondence, publications, 1974-1982 (Box 93, Folder 17-22)
  - Asian Committee for People's Organization (ACPO), 1987 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Asian Conference on Religion and Peace (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Asian Conference on Religion and Peace, Singapore, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 16-18)
  - Asian Conference on Religion and Peace, Bangkok, 1978- (Box 93, Folder 23)
  - Asian Conference on Women, Religion, and Family Laws; India, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - Asian Consultation on Resource Sharing, 1987 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Asian Consultation on the Meaning of the India Experience for Asia and the Asian Churches (sponsored by WCC/CCA/CIRSRS), Kerala, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 25)
  - Asian Cultural Forum on Development, 1979-1985 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Asian Ecumenical Conference on the Role of Health in Development of Nations, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 1-14)
  - Asian Institute for Liturgy and Music (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Asian Inter-religious Leaders Conference "Being Peace Makers in Asia Today," Thailand, 2007 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Asian Movement for Christian Unity (Box 79, Folder 23-24)
  - Asian Women's Resource Centre, 1984-1990 (Box 79, Folder 25-26)
  - Association for Theological Education in South East Asia/Foundation for Theological Education in South East Asia, 1983-1990 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Association of Christian Institutes for Social Concern in Asia, 1985-1990 (Box 79, Folder 28-29)
  - Association of Christian Universities and Colleges in Asia, 1990-1991 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Association of Directors of Christian Institutes for Social Concern in Asia, 1969-1974 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Association of South-East Asian Nations (ASEAN), 1977 (Box 99, Folder 21)
  - Australia Council of Churches, 1973-1976 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - Australia Council of Churches: 36th General Meeting in Melbourne, June 26-30, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Baptist Council on World Missions, 1974-1982 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Board for Education for Liberation (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - British Council of Churches: Christian Aid (1 of 2), 1974-1978 (Box 80, Folder 3-4)
  - Brot Fuer Die Welt (Bread for the World), 1972-1979 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Burma Council of Churches (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Canadian Council of Churches (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Caribbean Conference of Churches (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Youth Council of Thailand, 1982-1983 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - China Christian Council / China Religious Affairs Bureau (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Christian Broadcasting System (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Christian Institute for the Study of Religion and Society, India (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Christian Workers Fellowship: worship services, liturgical consultation, 1975, no date (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Church of Christ in Thailand, Consultation in Bangkok, October 19-22, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Church of North India, 1970-1971 (Box 80, Folder 14)